# **NORHALIZA BINTI ZABIDI**

## **PROFILE**



**Phone No** 

**Email** 

Address NO 65 KG NAI TEH, MUKIM PADANG TEMAK,

06300 KUALA NERANG, KEDAH 6017-6229086/+6013-4348046 haliza\_nur93@yahoo.com

931129-02-5782 IC No Race Malay Age 24 years old Religion Islam Date of Birth 29 November 1993 Gender **Female Nationality** Malaysian **Marital Status** Single Malay, English **Driving License** D/B2 Language

**Vision**To obtain a position as an Assistant Quantity Surveyor in an organization where in can utilize my skills and contribute towards the company's growth.

Career Objective Seeking for a permanent job placement especially in quantity survey. Expand my current skills set in construction industry either in consultant sector or contractor sector, and want

to be a professional and known person in industry one days.

## **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

Duration	Institution	Certification / Award	Result
2015 - 2017	UiTM Shah Alam	Degree in Quantity Surveyor (Hons)	CGPA : 2.97
2011 - 2014	UiTM Sri Iskandar Perak	Diploma in Quantity Surveyor	CGPA : 2.75
2009 - 2010	SMK Kuala Nerang	Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM)	7B 1C 1E

PERSONAL SKILL PERSONAL STRENGTH

Microsoft Office Microsoft Powerpoint Microsoft Excel Microsoft Publisher



- Fast learner and disciplined
- Hardworking and friendly
- Teamwork and task-oriented
- Able to multitask and work under pressure

# WORKING EXPERIENCES

Company	Position	Years
JURUUKUR BAHAN PSZ SDN BHD CHIN CHUN COMUNICATION MEXS COLLECTIONS KAS JURUUKUR BAHAN SDN BHD	Practical trainee Sales Assistant Sales Assistant Part time Qs	November 2013 - Mac 2014 April 2014 - JUN 2014 Jan 2017 - Mac 2017 April 2017

## SEMINARS, CONFERENCES AND COURSES ATTENDED

Programmes	Venue	Description
Mini Presentation of Applied Studies	UITM Shah Alam	Organized by a lecturers of quantity surveying Uitm Shah Alam to enhance student's skills in handling a projects. A gold medal winner for that exhibition.
Programme for QS registration scheme (PQRS)	UITM Shah Alam	Organized by a Lembaga Juruukur Bahan Malaysia together with Royal Intuition of Surveyors Malaysia and Uitm to encourage all Qs graduates to be part of the professional cluster agenda.
Participate in Academic Trip at Malaysian Marine and Heavy Engineering Holding Berhad (MMHE)	Pasir Gudang	To learn about heavy engineering industry

## **MISCELLANEOUS**

• Expected salary : RM 2000 ((can be negotiated)

Posses own transport : YesWilling to travel : Yes

Health status : No diseases, fit and healthy.

Expected to start working: FEBRUARY 2017

## **REFEREES**

#### DR Faridah Binti Muhammad Halil

Supervisor of Appilied Studies II Faculty of architecture, Planning and Surveyor Universiti Teknologi Mara (UiTM), Fakulti Seni Bina, Perancangan dan Ukur, Universiti Teknologi MARA 40450,Shah Alam

Selangor Darul Ehsan

Contact No.: +6017-2022145

### Sir Nasyairi bin Mat Nasir

Class Personal Advisor
Faculty of architecture, Planning and Surveyor
Universiti Teknologi Mara (UiTM),
Fakulti Seni Bina, Perancangan dan Ukur,
Universiti Teknologi MARA 40450,Shah Alam
Selangor Darul Ehsan

Contact No.: +6019-6665554

#### Hazalan bin Haron

Quantity Surveyor

Juruukur Bahan Psz Sdn Bhd

18, Jalan Zamrud 3, Taman Pelangi, 05150, Alor Setar,
Kedah, 05150, Malaysia

Research Advisor (Lecturer)

Faculty of architecture, Planning
Universiti Teknologi Mara (UiTM),
Fakulti Seni Bina, Perancangan of

Tel: +60 4-734 5809

#### DR Prof Madya Faridah Binti Yusuf

Research Advisor (Lecturer)
Faculty of architecture, Planning and Surveyor
Universiti Teknologi Mara (UiTM),
Fakulti Seni Bina, Perancangan dan Ukur,
Universiti Teknologi MARA 40450,Shah Alam
Selangor Darul Ehsan

Email: faridahyusuf@salam.uitm.edu.my